Guide to the Cynthia Harrison feminist document collection, 1921-2008 MS1005.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Mailings, magazines, newsletters, 1968-1995; Series 7 (Box 19, Box 20, Box 17, Box 18, Box 21, Box 22, Box 23, Box 24, Box 12, Box 11, Box 10, Box 9, Box 16, Box 15, Box 14, Box 13)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1982-1984; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Comment on Research/Action about Wo/Men, 1978 March; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Community Schools, Community School Workshop of Toronto, 1972 March; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Congressional Clearinghouse on Women's Rights, 1977; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Congressional Union, 1981; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Continuing Education, University of Massachusetts `, 1972 November; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Department of Health, Education, Welfare (HEW) newsletter, 1973 April 11; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Electric Circle, 1975; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - The Emergency Librarian, 1973-1975; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Equal Rights Monitor, 1976-1977; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Equal Rights newsletter, National Woman's Party, 1983-1988; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - The Everywoman's Center newsletter, University of Massachusetts, 1973 May; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Female Liberation Newsletter, Cambridge, MA, 1973 June; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Feminist Art Journal, 1972-1973; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - The Feminist Bulletin, Scarborough, New York, 1974 May; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - The Feminist Bulletin, Westchester Woman's Liberation Coalition, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Fifth Estate, 1973 August 3; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - The First Revolution: A journal of female liberation, 1971 July; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Focus: A journal for gay women, 1972 December; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - For Women Only, The Woman's Institute (TWI), 1973-1974; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - The Furies, 1972 January; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Focus on Women, The YWCA Women's Center of the Oranges, 1972-1973; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Gay Liberator, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Gold Flower, A Twin Cities Newspaper for Women, 1973 June; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Health Right, Women's Health Forum, 1974; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Her-self: Women's news journal, 1973-1974; MS1005.UA (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - In Touch, 1974 May; MS1005.UA (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Iowoman: An occassionally printed newsletter from the Iowa Commission on the Status of Women, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - The Ladder, 1972; MS1005.UA (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Lazette, 1973 April; MS1005.UA (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - The Lesbian Tide, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - The Liberated Grapevine: News of the Women's Liberation Center of Nassau County, 1973 May; MS1005.UA (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - The Liberator, 1972-1973; MS1005.UA (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Lilith: Newsletter of the Woman's Group of Suffolk Community College, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Majority Report 1973 [1/2], MS1005.UA (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Majority Report 1973 [2/2], MS1005.UA (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Majority Report 1974 [1/2], MS1005.UA (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Majority Report 1974 [2/2], MS1005.UA (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Majority Report 1975 [1/2], MS1005.UA (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Majority Report 1975 [2/2], MS1005.UA (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Majority Report 1976 [1/3], MS1005.UA (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Majority Report 1976 [2/3], MS1005.UA (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Majority Report 1976 [3/3], MS1005.UA (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Majority Report 1977 [1/3], MS1005.UA (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Majority Report 1977 [2/3], MS1005.UA (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Majority Report 1977 [3/3], MS1005.UA (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Majority Report 1978 [1/3], MS1005.UA (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Majority Report 1978 [2/3], MS1005.UA (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Majority Report 1978 [3/3], MS1005.UA (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Majority Report 1979, MS1005.UA (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Marin's Women's News Journal, 1973 July; MS1005.UA (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Marriage, Divorce and the Family, 1974 October 15; MS1005.UA (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - McMaster, Women's Liberation Movement, MS1005.UA (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Momma, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Mother Lode: A feminist paper, San Francisco, 1971-1972; MS1005.UA (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Motive, 1972; MS1005.UA (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Moving Out, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Ms. Foundation for Women, brochure, 1987 October; MS1005.UA (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - NARAL-National Abortion Rights Action League, 1983-1989; MS1005.UA (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - National Advisory Council on Women's Educational Programs, 1980-1981; MS1005.UA (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - National Advisory Committee on Women, 1963-1979; MS1005.UA (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - The National Association of Bank Women (NABW) Journal, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - National Organization for Non-Parents, 1973 August; MS1005.UA (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - National NOW Times-Newsletter 1978-1979, MS1005.UA (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - National NOW Times-Newsletter 1979, MS1005.UA (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - National NOW Times-Newsletter 1980 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - National NOW Times-Newsletter 1981 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - National NOW Times-Newsletter 1984-1986 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - National NOW Times-Newsletter 1987, MS1005.UA (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - National NOW Times-Newsletter 1988-1989, MS1005.UA (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - National Organization of Women (NOW), Action Center mailing on ERA, 1977-1978; MS1005.UA (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - National Organization of Women (NOW), The Equal Rights Amendment Supporter's Handbook, 1974 September; MS1005.UA (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - National Organization of Women (NOW), Essex County, 1972; MS1005.UA (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - National Organization of Women (NOW), national mailings, 1983-1990; MS1005.UA (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - National Organization of Women (NOW), San Diego chapter, 1975 April; MS1005.UA (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Network News - The Newsletter of the National Woman's Health Network, 1983; MS1005.UA (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Network of Saskatchewan Action Committee, status of women, 1973 October; MS1005.UA (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - New Directions for Women in New Jersey, 1972-1973; MS1005.UA (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - New Directions for Women in New Jersey, 1974-1975; MS1005.UA (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - New Directions for Women, 1975; MS1005.UA (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - New Directions for Women, 1976-1977; MS1005.UA (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - New Directions for Women, 1977-1978; MS1005.UA (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - New Directions for Women, 1978-1979; MS1005.UA (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - New Directions for Women, 1983-1988; MS1005.UA (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - The New Feminist, 1971-1973; MS1005.UA (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - News/Notes 4, The Feminist Press, 1973-1985; MS1005.UA (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - News and Notes About Women Public Officials, Center for the American Woman and Politics (CAWP), 1988-1990; MS1005.UA (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - The New York Teacher, MS1005.UA (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - NJ Division on Civil Rights, 1970-1972; MS1005.UA (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Notes from the Third Year: Women's Liberation, 1971; MS1005.UA (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - NOVA NOW ERA, task force, 1976; MS1005.UA (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - NOW Consciousness-Raising, NOW's National Task Force on Consciousness-Raising, 1976; MS1005.UA (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - NOW Countdown to Equality, 1981 National NOW Conference, National Organization of Women, 1981 October; MS1005.UA (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - NOW's Do It Now, newsletter 1972, National Organization of Women, MS1005.UA (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - NOW's Do It Now, newsletter 1973, National Organization of Women, MS1005.UA (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - NOW's Do It Now, newsletter 1974, National Organization of Women, MS1005.UA (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - NOW's Do It Now, newsletter 1975, National Organization of Women, MS1005.UA (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - NOW's Do It Now, newsletter 1976, MS1005.UA (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - NOW's Do It Now, newsletter 1977, National Organization of Women, MS1005.UA (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund's National Assembly on the Future of the Family Resource Book, 1979; MS1005.UA (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - The Now Washington Equal Times, National Organization of Women, 1985; MS1005.UA (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Off Our Backs: A woman's news journal 1971, MS1005.UA (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Off Our Backs: A woman's news journal 1972, MS1005.UA (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Off Our Backs: A woman's news journal 1973, MS1005.UA (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Off Our Backs: A woman's news journal 1974 [1/2], MS1005.UA (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Off Our Backs: A woman's news journal 1974 [2/2], MS1005.UA (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Off Our Backs: A woman's news journal 1975 [1/2], MS1005.UA (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Off Our Backs: A woman's news journal 1975 [2/2], MS1005.UA (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Off Our Backs: A woman's news journal 1976 [1/2], MS1005.UA (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Off Our Backs: A woman's news journal 1976 [2/2], MS1005.UA (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Off Our Backs: A woman's news journal 1977 [1/2], MS1005.UA (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Off Our Backs: A woman's news journal 1977 [2/2], MS1005.UA (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Off Our Backs: A woman's news journal 1978, MS1005.UA (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Ohio Woman: News for women from the Women's Services Division of the Ohio Bureau of Employment Services, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Prose: National Law Women's Newsletter, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - On Campus with Women, Association of American Colleges, 1973 May; MS1005.UA (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - On Our Way, 1972; MS1005.UA (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Ontario Department of Labor, Women's Bureau Career Selector, 1968-1969; MS1005.UA (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Ontario Department of Labor, Women's Bureau publications, 1969-1971; MS1005.UA (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - The Other Woman, 1972; MS1005.UA (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - The Other Woman, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - The Other Woman, 1974-1975; MS1005.UA (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Pandora: Seattle's Women's Newspaper, 1973 June 26; MS1005.UA (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - The Pedestal, 1972-1973; MS1005.UA (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvanians for Women's Rights (PWR) newsletter, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Population Association of America Women's Caucus, 1973-1975; MS1005.UA (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Prime Time: For the liberation of women in the prime of life..., 1973-1974; MS1005.UA (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Prologue: The journal of the National Archives, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Quest: A feminist quarterly, 1976-1977; MS1005.UA (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - The Second Wave: A magazine of the new feminism, 1971; MS1005.UA (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Shmate: A journal of progressive Jewish thought, 1982; MS1005.UA (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Siren: A newsletter of anarcho-feminism, MS1005.UA (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Sister: New Haven's women's liberation newsletter, 1973 May; MS1005.UA (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Sisters: A magazine by and for gay women, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Skirting the Capitol with Marian Ash, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Social Education, The Woman's Movement: What N.O.W.?, 1983 February; MS1005.UA (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Society of Women Engineers, newsletter, 1973 May; MS1005.UA (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Social Responsibilities Round Table (SRRT), A.L.A., 1973 Novemeber; MS1005.UA (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Speak Out, 1973-1974; MS1005.UA (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - The Spokeswoman [1/5], 1972-1975; MS1005.UA (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - The Spokeswoman [2/5], 1976; MS1005.UA (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - The Spokeswoman [3/5], 1977; MS1005.UA (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - The Spokeswoman [4/5], 1978; MS1005.UA (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - The Spokeswoman [5/5], 1979-1980; MS1005.UA (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - The Sportswoman, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - State Government News, The Council of State Governments, 1984 November; MS1005.UA (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Status of Women Council, Vancouver, 1972; MS1005.UA (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - The Status of Women in CUPE, Canadian Union of Public Employees, MS1005.UA (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Status of Women News, National Action Committee on the Status of Women, 1974 June; MS1005.UA (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Status of Women: Third Report of the Virginia Commission on the Status of Women to the Governor, the General Assembly and the Citizens of Virginia, 1976; MS1005.UA (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Subscription offer, Feminist Issues: A journal of feminist social and political theory, 1985; MS1005.UA (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Take One: Women in Film, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Texas Citizens for Abortion Education, 1972 March (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - The Texas Woman, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Transition: Women's Reousrce Center, 1971-1973; MS1005.UA (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Triple Jeopardy: Racism, imperialism, sexism, 1972; MS1005.UA (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - UN Centre for Social Development and Humanitarian Affairs' Newsletter on the Status of Women, 1972; MS1005.UA (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Union WAGE, Woman's Alliance to Gain Equality, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Update: Congressional Caucus for Woman's Issues, 1985; MS1005.UA (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Velvet Fist, 1970-1972 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Washington Area Women's Center, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - WEAL conventions/conferences, Women's Equity Action League, 1973-1978; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - WEAL Educational and Legal Defense Fund, Women's Equity Action League, 1975-1987; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - WEAL Facts, Women's Equity Action League, 1982-1984; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - WEAL Informed, Women's Equity Action League, 1984-1988; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - WEAL mailers, Women's Equity Action League, 1973-1988; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - WEAL National Capitol Newsletter, Women's Equity Action League, 1976-1979; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - WEAL: New Jersey, Women's Equity Action League, 1975; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - WEAL's New Jersey Wealer, 1974-1975; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - WEAL News, national newsletter, Women's Equity Action League, 1973-1979; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - WEAL: Virginia, Women's Equity Action League, 1976-1978; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - WEAL Washington Report, Women's Equity Action League [1/2], 1973-1981; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - WEAL Washington Report,Women's Equity Action League [2/2], 1982-1989; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - WEECN Network News and Notes, Women's Educational Equity Communications Network, 1978; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Whole Woman, 1973 July 3; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Windsor Woman, 1972-1973; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - WLDF News, Woman's Legal Defense Fund, 1983; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - The Woman Activist: An action bulletin for women's rights, 1976 August; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - The Woman Activist - Virginia, 1973-1976; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Woman Power: A monthly report on fair employment practices for women, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Woman Power: A quarterly newsletter of the Committee on Women in Social Welfare, National Association of Social Workers, Inc., 1974; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Woman's World, 1971; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Womankind, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Womanpower: A special issue of Manpower Magazine, 1975 November; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Womanspace Journal, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Women: A journal of liberation [1/6], 1969; MS1005.UA (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Women: a journal of liberation [2/6], 1970; MS1005.UA (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Women: a journal of liberation [3/6], 1971; MS1005.UA (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Women: a journal of liberation [4/6], 1972-1974; MS1005.UA (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Women: a journal of liberation [5/6], 1974-1976; MS1005.UA (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Women: a journal of liberation [6/6], 1976-1978; MS1005.UA (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Women and Revolution, 1974; MS1005.UA (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Women & Work, 1973 March; MS1005.UA (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Women in Communications, Inc., 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Women in the Arts (WIA) newsletter, 1973 November; MS1005.UA (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Women Office Workers (WOW), 1976; MS1005.UA (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - "Women's Bureau," Canada Department of Labor, 1969-1971; MS1005.UA (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Woman's Center Newsletter, Poughkeepsie, New York, 1972-1973; MS1005.UA (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Women's Center News, YWCA of Greater Rhode Island, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Women's Educational & Industrial Union, Boston, MA, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Women's Educational Equity Act Program, Annual Report, 1980; MS1005.UA (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Women's Liberation Union Newsletter, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Women's Place-Newfoundland Status of Women Council Newsletter, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Women's Political Times, 1981-1988; MS1005.UA (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Women's Rights Law Reporter [1/6], 1972-1973; MS1005.UA (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Women's Rights Law Reporter [2/6], 1974; MS1005.UA (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Women's Rights Law Reporter [3/6], 1975; MS1005.UA (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Women's Rights Law Reporter [4/6], 1976-1977; MS1005.UA (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Women's Rights Law Reporter [5/6], 1978; MS1005.UA (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Women's Rights Law Reporter [6/6], 1979-1980; MS1005.UA (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Women's Studies Newsletter, Clearinghouse on Women's Studies, The Feminist Press, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Women's Studies Quarterly, 1984; MS1005.UA (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Women's Track & Field World, 1973 June; MS1005.UA (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Women's Voice of Greater Hartford, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - The World Conference of the UN, Decade for Women 1980, US Department of State, MS1005.UA (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - 9 to 5 Newsletter for Boston Area Office Workers, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - 13th Moon Writing Organization for Women at the City College of New York, 1973; MS1005.UA (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - 51% A Paper of Joyful Noise for the Majority Sex, 1971-1972; MS1005.UA (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Manuscript research, 1923-1988; Series 8 (Box 24, Box 25, Box 37, Box 28, Box 29, Box 26, Box 27, Box 32, Box 33, Box 30, Box 31, Box 35, Box 34, Box 36)
  Arranged alphabeticallyArrangement Note
  This series consists of photocopies of primary sources (reports, correspondence, publications, etc.) as well as other original primary source documentation used by Professor Harrison while researchign her 1988 book On Account of Sex: The Politics of Women's Issues, 1945-1968. Content relating to the Presdient's Commission on the Status of Women and the activities of the Women's Bureau are heavily represented, and span from the 1940's to the 1960's.
  - AFL, 1943-1979; Series 8 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Appointments for women 1964-, 1961-1968; Series 8 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Background (1920-1960), 1972-1979; Series 8 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Black women-Civil Rights Movement, 1963; Series 8 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Birth control & abortion 1960s, 1962-1966; Series 8 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Birth Control Handbook, 1969-1971; Series 8 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - BPW convention 1988, Series 8 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Campaign 1948, includes platforms, 1940-1948; Series 8 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Campaigns 1952, includes platforms, Series 8 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Campaigns 1956, includes platform, 1956-1957; Series 8 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Campaign 1968, Series 8 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - CBSFEI, 1977-1978; Series 8 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Civil Service Commission 1964- [1/2], 1964-1966; Series 8 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Civil Service Commission 1964- [2/2], 1966-1968; Series 8 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Conference on family life 1948, 1946-1948; Series 8 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Consumer Council 1964-, 1963-1967; Series 8 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Daycare 1940-1972 [1/2], 1940-1959; Series 8 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Daycare 1940-1972 [2/2], 1960-1972; Series 8 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Daycare 1945- (WWII and postwar years), 1973-1974; Series 8 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Daycare ref. file, 1952 report, 1957 February 19; Series 8 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Daycare 1964-, 1963-1968; Series 8 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Democratic National Committee (sources not used in manuscript), 1946-1967; Series 8 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Douglas, Helen Gahagan (HGD) poll tax, 1947; Series 8 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Executive Order 11246 LBJ, 1965-1967; Series 8 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Federal Women's Award, 1962-1968; Series 8 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Female Employment 1961-1963, 1961-1968; Series 8 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Homemakers for Equal Rights, 1976; Series 8 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Household workers, 1950-1978; Series 8 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - International misc. [1/2], 1946-1965; Series 8 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - International misc. [2/2], 1965-1968; Series 8 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Job Corps, 1964-1967; Series 8 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Johnson Background [1/2], 1963-1978; Series 8 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Johnson Background [2/2], 1968-1979; Series 8 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Jury Selection 1966, 1965-1971; Series 8 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Kennedy Background, 1946-1978; Series 8 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Labor, 1947-1986; Series 8 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Maternal and Infant Health, 1945-1948; Series 8 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Misc. Ch. 6, 1962-1981; Series 8 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Mrs. Roosevelt, 1962; Series 8 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - National Service for Women, 1962-1967; Series 8 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - National Women's Committee for Civil Rights, 1963; Series 8 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Natinoal Women's Party History 1913-1974, 1979; Series 8 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - PSEW, 1977-1978; Series 8 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - PCSW Arthur Goldberg, 1985; Series 8 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - PCSW "Basic Principles" 2nd Meeting, 1962 April 19; Series 8 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - PCSW Committees Civ. and Pol. Rights [2/6], 1962-1963; Series 8 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - PCSW Committees Civ. and Pol. Rights [3/6], 1963; Series 8 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - PCSW Committees Civ. and Pol. Rights [4/6], 1963; Series 8 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - PCSW Committees Civ. and Pol. Rights [1/6], 1962-1964; Series 8 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - PCSW Committees Civ. and Pol. Rights [5/6], 1962-1963; Series 8 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - PCSW Committees Civ. and Pol. Rights [6/6], 1963 June 7; Series 8 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - PCSW Committees Education [1/2], 1960-1962; Series 8 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - PCSW Committees Education [2/2], 1962-1963; Series 8 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - PCSW Committees Fed. Emp. [1/3], 1947-1962; Series 8 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - PCSW Committees Fed. Emp. [2/3], 1962; Series 8 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - PCSW Committee Fed. Emp. [3/3], 1963; Series 8 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - PCSW Committees Home and Community [1/3], 1962; Series 8 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - PCSW Committees Home and Community [2/3], 1962-1963; Series 8 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - PCSW Committees Home and Comm. [3/3], 1963; Series 8 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - PCSW Committees P. L. L. [1/3], 1949-1962; Series 8 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - PCSW Committees P. L. L. [2/3], 1962-1963; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - PCSW Committees P. L. L. [3/3], 1963; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - PCSW Committees on Priv. Emp. [1/4], 1960-1962; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - PCSW Committees on Priv. Emp. [2/3], 1962; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - PCSW Committees on Priv. Emp. [3/4], 1962; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - PCSW Committees Priv. Emp. [4/4], 1963; Series 8 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - PCSW Committees SIT [1/5], 1958-1962; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - PCSW Committees SIT [2/5], 1962; Series 8 (Box 32, Folder 2)